<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on The Objective Perspective.  A blog for the Mindful. </title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on The Objective Perspective.  A blog for the Mindful. </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech Fires in the workplace, and how to easily avoid them.</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/techfires/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/techfires/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned-from-a-25-year-network-engineer-veteran&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned from a 25-Year Network Engineer, Veteran&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hey there, fellow network enthusiasts! As a network veteran, I&amp;rsquo;m here to share some super valuable tips on how to minimize downtime in the workplace. After all, who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love a productive workday without those pesky IT issues getting in the way? Many of these are hard lessons I had to learn on my own.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-stats-are-scary-but-honest&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Stats are Scary (But Honest)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s face it: downtime can be a major productivity killer. According to a report by IT Brand Pulse (1), 80% of businesses experience at least one hour of downtime per week, resulting in an average loss of $5,000 per minute! That&amp;rsquo;s a whole lotta money just sitting idle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting your foot in the door - Tips from an IT Vet</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/techfoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/techfoot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-land-a-job-in-it-without-prior-work-experience&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How To Land a Job in IT Without Prior Work Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Getting hired can be difficult enough, but getting hired without any experience is damn near impossible. After all, how can you get hired without experience in order to obtain the experience you need in order to get hired in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I hope to answer that question for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will be writing this with the assumption that you do not have any work history, a fresh degree, and not a whole lot of real world experience. Please pick and choose what applies to your unique situation according to your skill set and what you feel comfortable with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why AI is a Really Bad Idea</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/aibad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/aibad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Before I take any digs at artificial intelligence (as Hollywood portrays it and as we fear it), allow me to express that I am all for using technology to benefit us. Artificial intelligence, as it currently exists, is useful. As a technical tool, it&amp;rsquo;s downright phenomenal. I should be a fan of technology; after all, I spent the better half of my life as a network engineer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I&amp;rsquo;m not. Not because it makes my life difficult or tied to any otherworldly belief system, but because I can see where this is heading, and it&amp;rsquo;s not good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Our New Internet Old Extraterrestrial Technology?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/alientcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/alientcp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Conspiracy theories, the not-so-serious or non-political kind, serve as a mental break from work, much like recess time did in grade school. Pondering their merit, whether factual or not, is beside the point. As humans, we&amp;rsquo;re drawn to mysteries and &lt;em&gt;what-ifs&lt;/em&gt; in life. We enjoy daydreaming about an Undiscovered Country that only requires our time for refuge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;nothing-to-see-here-move-along&#34;&gt;Nothing To See Here. Move Along&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I mention &lt;em&gt;Roswell, NM&lt;/em&gt;, our thoughts instantly transform into a UFO crash—an event (&lt;em&gt;&amp;rsquo;non-event&amp;rsquo;&lt;/em&gt;) that took place in 1947. Alongside this image, we envision countless roadside diners in New Mexico displaying flying saucer logos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
